I'm gonna kill you.
[Roars]
[People screaming]
[Man groaning] Now!
Go! Go! Go! We got your back!
[Gunfire]
We are going to war!
All: Yes, sir!
[Birds
["Weird Al" Yankovic's "Another
One Rides the plays in distance]
♪♪
[Rhythmic clapping]
Riding in the bus ♪
And the place ♪
♪
Couldn't find a seat, ♪
With the perverts ♪
It was smelling like ♪
[Insects chirping]
[Birds chirping]
[Hammer clanging]
[Indistinct conversations]
[Clanging continues]
♪♪
[Conversations continue]
[Air hissing]
♪♪
10:28.
When I first met him...
Jesus said that my world was
gonna get a whole lot bigger.
♪♪
Well, we found that world.
We found each other.
That..."bigger world"
is ours by right.
That we've come together
for it, all of us...
it's that much more true
-- it's ours by right.
[Walkers growling in distance]
Any person who would live
in peace and fairness,
who would find common ground...
it's their right, too.
♪♪
[Walkers growling in distance]
Down.
But those who use and take and
kill to carve out the world
and make it theirs
alone -- we end them.
♪♪
We don't...celebrate it.
We don't have shame
about it, either.
♪♪
There's only one person
who has to die...
and I will kill him myself.
I will.
[Walkers growling in distance]
[Pen clicks]
♪♪
[Growling continues]
[Arrow fires]
♪♪
But if it's the others...
the others who prop him
up, stand by his side,
even those who just
look the other way --
so be it.
10:28.
[Walkers growling in distance]
Then... we keep making
the world bigger.
♪♪
Together.
Ezekiel: Together.
Bound forever!
To quote The Bard, "For he today
that sheds his blood with me
shall be my brother."
♪♪
For she today...
my sister.
[Shiva roars]
Maggie: We've practiced.
We've been through it
over and over again.
We all know the plan
doesn't end this morning.
That we may have to live
in uncertainty for days,
maybe more.
That we have to keep our
faith in each other.
If we can hold on to that
with everything we have,
the future is ours.
is ours.
♪♪
[Walkers growling
loudly in distance]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
♪
And another comes on ♪
♪♪
There's a suitcase ♪
♪
There's a smelly old bum ♪
Well, I think I'm missing ♪
♪
And I think this bus ♪
To let a couple more ♪
[Mid-tempo music plays]
♪♪
== Sync, Corrected
by Prabhat Rana ==
[Wind
[Wind blowing
[Wind blowing softly]
[Insects chirping]y]
[Brakes squeal]
[Engine shuts off]
[Door creaks]
[Chirping continues]
[Birds chirping]
Man: Hi.  [Can clatters]
Yeah. I-I'm okay.
I mean... I'm not, but...
I've been shot at.
Someone threw a microwave at me.
So I-I'm just gonna say
something my mom used to say
and hope for the best here.
"Whatever you have of good,
spend on the traveler."
My mom said that -- that
helping the traveler,
the person without a home
-- that's everything.
I'm sure you've seen things,
been through things,
that you don't trust people.
I get it. I get it.
I don't, either.
I've been through things, too.
My mom -- she also said that,
"May my mercy prevail
over my wrath."
[Scoffs] It's not all my mom.
That -- That one --
That's from the Quran.
Probably shouldn't
have said that.
I don't even know you,
but I ha-- I haven't
eaten in a few days.
You might not even be real.
♪♪
Hands up.
Listen.
I'm gone.
Huh? It's cool.
I just --
I just wanted some --
e-even just some food.
[Gunshots]
♪♪
We were supposed to meet
at the intersection.
♪♪
I shot over his head.
I just wanted him gone.
He said that he was --
I heard what he said.
Most of it.
But he could've
been one of them.
Like a spy?
[Gun drops in holster]
I shot above his head.
one of them, I hope he makes it.
It's not gonna be enough, Dad.
Enough what?
Hope.
[Sighs]
[Walker growling]
♪♪
[Silenced gunshot]
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Thuds softly]
[Door rattling]
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Grunts]
[Body thuds]
♪♪
[Shuddering breath]
30 minutes. Everyone's ready.
♪♪
Are you?
It's one person who
brought it to this.
One person.
It always starts
with one person.
This did.
What we're doing here now.
This -- This isn't about me.
Yes. It isn't.
You made it like that.
♪♪
[Engine revs]
[Engine revving]
♪♪
[Engine shuts off]
[Engine starts]
Come here.
[Engine starts, revs]
[Brakes squeal]
This is the end of it.
♪♪
[Engine revs]
I know you wanted
to go with him.
♪♪
I did, too.
Everything hurts.
♪♪
But I'll help you
defend this place.
me? Oh, yeah.
show.
[Scoffs]
Okay...
♪♪
You'll see.
[Walker growling]
[Rick whistles]
[Groans]
[Body thuds]
♪♪
[Breathing heavily]
What are you up to, Rick?
[Coughs]
You think you're
gonna take us on?
[Coughs, groans]
I saw you...
beggin'.
Crying.
You're gonna beg again, Rick.
[Coughs]
[Breathing heavily]
Your -- Your boy's gonna die.
[Coughing]
♪♪
[Walker growling]
Aah!
[Flesh tearing]  No, no, no!
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Indistinct conversations]
[Brakes squeal]
♪♪
Andy: Sure are a lot of us here.
I got your back.
Really? You just met me.
all just met each other.
[Indistinct conversations]
Aaron: Are you praying?
I always meant to start.
Better late than never.
♪♪
Jerry: Here.
Over your sternum.
No, I'm going back
with Maggie after.
Dude. Sternum.
Duuuuuude.
Rick: You up to this?
Maggie: I got the Hilltop to
stand against the Saviors.
I need to be there.
At least for the first part.
They say you can wage war
through the second trimester.
[Chuckles]
I've been fighting
since the farm.
Can't stop now.
How about tomorrow?
You been thinking about
what that looks like?
Yes, I have.
I don't know if I
can wait for it.
Just one more fight.
And I'm gonna be there.
At least for the first part.
Ezekiel: I'm told the
Hilltop lost their doctor.
An obstetrician, no less.
We have a doctor in the Kingdom.
A woman of talent. Join us.
We'll get ours back.
[Laughs]
Yes, Jesus.
Yes, you will.
As sure as the day
defeats the night.
And on this day, we begin
to reshape this world
for your child and the
children to come.
So let's get started.
♪♪
[Sighs]
What?
Hilltop's lucky to have you.
♪♪
You showed me how to be
someone worth following.
Good.
♪♪
After this...
you.
♪♪
Here we go.
10...
9...
8...
7...6...
5...
4...
3...
2...
1.
♪♪
Shit.
[Wind whistling]
No. There.
Tara: Okay.
Close enough.
All right, let's go. Got it?
Yeah.  [Engine starts, revs]
♪♪
[Walkers growling]
Woman: It went up
towards the herdway.
Dwight: Go big. 2 cars, 10 guns.
We're not messing
around, not now.
You take the Sister route.
It's locked down.
Do you think it was them?
Nah.
Probably something left over,
maybe under one of the bodies.
I want some bang bang, Dwighty.
I want some scream scream.
I want blood.
♪♪
Well...
maybe you'll get lucky.
♪♪
Carol: How close are we?
Daryl: Close.
[Walkers growling in distance]
[Silenced gunshots]
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Brakes squeal]
[Engines shut off]
[Vehicle doors open]
[Growling continues]
♪♪
[Guns cock]
[Gunshots]
♪♪
[Doorknob creaks]
Well, shit.
I'm sorry.
♪♪
I was in a meeting.
[Insects
[Insects chirping]
[Creaking softly]
["Weird Al" Yankovic's "Another
One Rides the plays in distance]
♪
And another comes on ♪
Mnh.
Another one rides the
bus, hey, hey! ♪
♪
♪  You turned off the alarm.
They can manage without
you for one morning.
Carl: We're all playing hooky.
All of us?  The window
doesn't open, ♪
Hey, I didn't put that song on.
Mm. [Chuckles]
[Walkers growling in distance]
Negan: Well, shit.
I'm sorry.
I was in a meeting.
[Growling continues]
I see you got your little
mudflaps with you.
So I'm not exactly
feelin' a reason
for us to try throwin'
lead at each other.
I care about my people.
I don't want to just march
them into the line of fire
because I want play "my
dick is bigger than yours."
It is.
We both know it.
But I'm also comfortable enough
to accept the fact if it wasn't.
I'm certainly not gonna let my
people die over that shit...
...like you're about to.
♪♪
So, Rick, what the
hell can I do for you?
Dwight.
♪♪
Your name's Simon.
You're Gavin.
♪♪
And you...
Regina.
Rick, I'd feel remiss
if --  Rick: No.
I know who you are.
♪♪
Listen, you five.
The Saviors inside.
All of you have a
chance to survive here.
To survive this.
You all can live
if you surrender.
Can't guarantee it
any time but now.
Right now.
[Walkers growling in distance]
♪♪
Tara: Shit.
Could that thing set it off?
Morgan: I got it.
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
Negan: So they surrender...
and you and your little piss
patrol doesn't kill them.
That sounds like a good deal!
♪♪
What about me, Rick?
I told you. Twice.
You know what's going to happen.
I do.
know what's gonna happen.
You don't.
You have no idea the shit
that's about to go down.
Let me ask you
something, Rick --
Do you think you have the
numbers for this fight?
♪♪
You don't.
Simon?
♪♪
Of course that's where he went.
Negan: What do you have to say
to the Rick and the
piss patrol, Gregory?
The Hilltop stands with
Negan and the Saviors.
Any resident of the
Hilltop who takes up arms
or who supports this ultimatum
against the Sanctuary
or any of the Saviors,
for that matter --
they will no longer be
welcome in the colony.
And?
Their families
will be thrown out
and will be left to
fend for themselves.
And?
Go home now.
Or you won't have a
home to go back to.
♪♪
You do what you need to do.
All I have at the Hilltop
are a bunch of books and
an old lobster bib.
♪♪
Negan: You heard the man.
Go back to separating
wheat and shit
or whatever the hell
it is you people do.
Doesn't look like
anyone's goin', does it?
♪♪
Hilltop stands with --
The Hilltop stands with Maggie!
♪♪
[Walker growling]
I feel...
like I invested a lot in you,
and I am very, disappointed.
[Grunting]
[Body thudding]
♪♪
[Engine revs]
[Wire rattles]
[Explosions in distance]
♪♪
[Walkers growling in distance]
Sounds like shit is
goin' down, Rick.
♪♪
You "lieutenants..."
you're gonna have to
make up your minds.
Maybe we can take a
time-out here --
No. This has to happen now.
This is the only way.
[Growling continues]
♪♪
You're gonna make me count.
[Chuckles]
Okay.
I'm counting.
10!
9!
8!
7!
[Gun cocks]
[Gunshots]
[Gunfire]
♪♪
[Walkers growling in distance]
Carol: It's started.
Daryl: Yeah. It was
always gonna be that way.
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
Tara: Pleasure doing
business with you.
♪♪
Beat 'em.
We will.
♪♪
Be careful.
[Engine starts]
Shit, this is gonna be fun.
[Growling continues]
No, it isn't.
It's better than lettin'
things be, though, right?
♪♪
Yeah. It is.
[Growling continues]
♪♪
Now!
[Gunfire]
♪♪
[Walkers growling]
[Gunfire]
[Horn honks]
[Engine revs]
♪♪
[Gunshot, explosion]
[Gunfire continues]
♪♪
[Gunshot, explosion]
[Engine revs]
♪♪
[Gunshot, explosion]
[Gunfire]
[Gunshot]
Go!
[Gunfire]
[Gunshot, explosion]
[Gunfire continues]
♪♪
[Growling]
[Gunshot, explosion]
♪♪
[Walkers growling]
[Gunfire]
♪♪
[Explosion]
[Walkers growling, gunfire]
[Groans]
♪♪
Gabriel: Rick!
[Distorted gunfire]
♪♪
He's not going anywhere!
Rick!
Rick! We have to go!
Rick! He's not going anywhere!
We have to leave now!
It's not about you, right?
Not about you.
Come here.
[Gunfire continues]
♪♪
[Camera shutter clicks, whirs]
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Engine starts]
[Tires screech]
No, no. Wait. Wait.
Whoa!
[Groans]
♪♪
Shit.
[Gun cocks]
[Gunfire]
♪♪
I'm gonna get you out of here.
We just have to wait
for our moment.
Thank you, Father.
Thank God.
Sure, whatever.
[Gunfire]
The -- The -- The shots
-- they're too close!
Why are they me?
[Gunshots]
♪♪
Wait.  [Gunfire continues]
Hey, hey!
Wait!
♪♪
[Groans]
[Engine starts]
[Walkers growling]
[Gunfire continues]
[Birds
[Birds chirping]
♪♪
[Car door closes]
We can wait some more.
We can't.
He stopped to get me.
How's that?
Negan. [Sighs]
He was on the ground.
I was trying to kill him, and
Gabriel stopped to get me.
♪♪
We gotta start out.
You all right?
♪♪
[Chuckles]
This isn't about me.
Let's go.
Yeah.
[Whistles]
[Engine starts]
♪♪
We were gonna start with taking
out the guards with arrows.
You think you can still
hit them through that?
♪♪
I wouldn't bet on it.
[Arrow fires]  [Grunts]
♪♪
[Gates creaking]
[Gunfire]
♪♪
[Metal scrapes,
clattering]  Down!
[Explosion]
[Walkers growling]
♪♪
[Growling continues]
[Breathing heavily]
Negan: I hope you got
your shitting pants on.
♪♪
What?
Your shittin' pants.
I hope you're wearing
them right now...
♪♪
...'cause you...
are about to shit your pants.
♪♪
[Growling continues]
Daddy!
[Chuckling] Hey!
[Smooches]
They made a big owl
for the party!
What?
People are taking this
festival extremely seriously.
A big owl?  ♪
It's outside. [Gasps]
They're gonna get you.
Never. Should we go see?
♪
I'm not afraid of a big owl.
How big is it?
[Indistinct conversation]
♪
[Mid-tempo music plays]
♪♪
[Chuckles]
[Birds chirping]
My mercy...
prevails...
over my wrath.
[Chuckles]
♪♪
I don't want to wait
for it anymore.
You don't either
-- Yeah, I know.
So we don't have to wait for it.
If we start tomorrow
right now...
with everything we've beaten,
everything we've endured,
everything we've risen above,
everything we've become...
If we start tomorrow
right now...
no matter what comes next...
we've won.
We've already won.
[Crowd cheers]
== Sync, Corrected
by Prabhat Rana ==
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org